There's a good reason it's the road less travelled.
The Fearway is a horror, mystery film directed by Robert Gajic.
A young couple travelling down the freeway seem to be unable to get off the road
after being hunted by someone intent on keeping them on the road.
Sarah, played by Shannon Dalonzo.
Old Woman, played by Eileen Dietz.
The Manager, played by Simon Phillips.
Waitress, played by Jessica Gray.
Michael, played by Justin Gordon.
Bus Boy, played by John D. Hickman.
The Fearway is a 2023 American horror film directed by Robert Gajic and starring
Shannon Dalonzo, Eileen Dietz, Simon Phillips, and Jessica Gray.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.